inspiringgreatness.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy | Inspiring Greatness...

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should you be asked to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Here is a list of the information we collect, and why it is necessary to collect it:  
Name and basic contact details, including email address

This information is used:  
* to provide you with the services which you request  
* to maintain our accounts  
* to enable your enquiries be answered  
* for marketing our services, products, contests, give-aways

What Is Done With Information Gathered :

This information is required to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
* Internal record keeping  
* To improve products and services offered  
* To send promotional emails and newsletters notifying you about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided us.

Disclosure to Government:  
We may be required to give information to legal authorities if they so request, or if they have the proper authorization such as a search warrant or court order  
We hold on to your personal information for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which it was collected, unless otherwise required by law. If you request that we stop sending you updates and other communications or delete your information, we will honour your request and keep the minimum amount of information possible to prevent fraud and to help ensure that you are not contacted again.

SECURITY:  
* We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected whether online or in paper format.   
* Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of my website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. I ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

HOW COOKIES ARE USED:  
* A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   
* Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.   
* You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, @InspiringGreatness has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, @InspiringGreatness will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.  
Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are not allowed to access our service.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting @InspiringGreatness, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these third party websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
Inspiring Greatness may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 25, 2018.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of @InspiringGreatness then you may contact us at support@inspiringgreatness.com

This privacy policy was generated by the [Easy Privacy Policy](http://europeancruiseadvisor.com/ "Easy Privacy Policy homepage") plugin for WordPress.

Last updated Sat, 18 Aug 2018 01:45
